Preliminary Inventory to the Toshio Kimura Letters, 1942-1945
Hoover Institution Archives
Toshio Kimura Letters,
1942-1945
73048
Kimura, Toshio
1 folder (0.1 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Relates to conditions in the relocation camp and prospects for release. Includes letters from Mrs. T. Kimura.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
Biographical/Historical Note
Japanese American interned at Heart Mountain, Wyoming, Relocation Camp, 1942-1945.
Scope and Content
Correspondence between Mr. Toshio Kimura, his wife Midori, and daughter June, with Mrs. "Nancy" Storm (Gantvoort), and Mrs. L. Cochran, 1942-1945
Access Points
Heart Mountain Relocation Center, Wyoming.; Japanese Americans--Evacuation and relocation, 1942-1945.; World War, 1939-1945.; World War, 1939-1945--United States.; United States.
Container List
- Toshio to Nancy, 1942 August 28 (Folder 1)
- Midori to Nancy, 1942 September 25
- Toshio to Nancy, 1942 October 7
- Toshio to Nancy, 1942 November 4
- Midori to Nancy, 1942 November 4
- Midori to Mrs. Cochran, 1942 November 4
- Toshio to Nancy, 1943 January 6
- Toshio to Nancy, 1943 March 24
- Toshio to Nancy, 1943 July 29
- Toshio and Midori to Nancy, 1943 October 9
- June to Nancy, 1943 October 15
- Toshio to Nancy, 1943 October 31
- Toshio to Nancy, 1943 November 14
- Toshio to Nancy, 1943 November 23
- Toshio to Nancy, 1943 December 27
- Toshio to Nancy, 1944 February 19
- Toshio to Nancy, 1944 March 8
- Toshio to Nancy, 1944 May 25
- Toshio to Nancy, 1944 September 20
- Toshio to Nancy, 1944 October 8
- Midori to Nancy, 1945 January 8
- Midori to Nancy, 1945 May 6
- Midori to Mrs. Cochran and family, 1945 August 15